Rajesh ji is picking you,
Virendra ji, see my eyes are on Tata
Communication since yesterday, Tata, I
got a break out yesterday, today there is a follow through, so
a small trade is being formed here, keep the stop loss
around 1290 and its target
according to me is at least 1335 to 1340, it will reach here, firstly
it has not moved and if it has moved then it has
moved very strongly, so today's exit from
Tata Company,
so at this time the
trends for you are in difference to a great extent,
Tata Communication, let's go to
Manas, Manas, your
trade will be
and that rally of buying in granules,
he has
taken out a buy above that after consultation with both of them, so the current level
can be 283, are you putting a stoppage, the
target is ₹95 ahead of 295
and here you can take another option of ₹290, you
can buy, for the time of 12:30,
from ok,
take one more here, so many pharma stocks are currently
trading, the
first of your train is ahead
1460 today I tried my hand at United Breweries,
see what is the joke of it, right now
Breweries is coming here at 1460,
doing well yesterday, it is trying to break the highest cluster of the last five sessions,
Prakash Sir, just look at RBL Bank once, I mean
gradually its mouth is
becoming sharp,
how strong is the candle of the day before yesterday,
I think
now this entire supply cluster from January 2030
till, scrolling
download channel, that biceps is happening, sir,
some short term is visible
but the reluctant will have to place a
very good
fight
of 162 and it is possible that it may go up to 170,
but a buy single has been generated in the chart
and it is going up to
655, the
peak light is doing well on your screen
and
what is 2654 doing on the weekly chart, weekly
best movie Asia Paints Kansai, all of them are
good
ideas website